--- FULL FIRESTORE DATA ---
{
  "claim": "Drinking hot water cures dengue.",
  "id": "message_id_1772902073",
  "confidence": 0.95,
  "timestamp": "2026-03-07 22:17:53.233228+00:00",
  "explanation": "The provided evidence does not support the claim that drinking hot water cures dengue. The text mentions 'warm water foot soaking' as a supportive intervention for managing hyperthermia (fever) in dengue patients, which is an external application, not for consumption. While various other beverages like barley water, coconut water, chaas, and lemon water are discussed as beneficial for hydration, symptom management (e.g., reducing fever, supporting liver function), or boosting immunity during dengue, none are stated to cure the disease. Crucially, the evidence explicitly states 'Myth: Coconut water cures dengue. Reality:', indicating that even other beneficial drinks do not offer a cure. Dengue requires proper medical management, and these drinks are presented as supportive measures, not curative treatments.",
  "audio_file": "test_audio.mp3",
  "verdict": "False",
  "transcription": "drinking hot water cure's dengue",
  "counter_message": "Drinking hot water does NOT cure dengue. While some drinks aid hydration & symptoms, dengue needs medical care. Don't fall for false cures!"
}
